export const questions = [
  {
    id: "1",
    question: `What was the first fruit that was eaten on the moon? `,
    a: "Orange",
    b: "Apple",
    c: "Peach",
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: `When people are frightened, their ears produce more what? `,
    a: "Earwax",
    b: "Water",
    c: "Pox",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question: `What sport has been played on the moon? `,
    a: "Tennis",
    b: "Basketball",
    c: "Golf",
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question: `When held to ultraviolet light, what animal's urine glows in the dark?`,
    a: "Cat",
    b: "Dog",
    c: "Bird",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: `From which language did the word "Ketchup" come from?`,
    a: "French",
    b: "Chinese",
    c: "Spanish",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: `What color is the "black box" in an airplane?`,
    a: "Blue",
    b: "Black",
    c: "Orange",
    answer: "c",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: `What ailment kills the most fruit flies?`,
    a: "Diarrhea",
    b: "Constipation",
    c: "Fever",
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: `In Alaska, it's legal to shoot bears, but illegal to do what?`,
    a: "Throw stones",
    b: "Wake one up",
    c: "Take pictures",
    answer: "b",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question: `Where were the first fortune cookies invented?a`,
    a: "San Francisco",
    b: "Seattle",
    c: "Texas",
    answer: "a",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: `What does the term "piano" actually mean?`,
    a: "To be played to an audience",
    b: "To be played softly",
    c: "To be played slowly",
    answer: "b",
  },
];
